翻译校对       Mam
日  听      マキ
日听校对       Syura
翻译        葉隠
时间轴       鬼 忻奈
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
"Library Room #4"
There are four whole library rooms,
so why do they all have to be noisy?
四つも図書室があるのに
なんでどこも騒がしいんだ
Mother, up in Heaven,
it's been ten years now, huh?
天国のお母さん
あれからもう十年になりますね
It seems like the children of rich people
come to school for the fun of it.
お金持ちの子供って
なんか学校には遊びに来てるみたいです
"Music Room #3"
An unused music room...
楽室
I guess this is about the only place
where I can study in peace and quiet.
静かに勉強できんのはここぐらいか
いらっしゃいませ
- Welcome!
When I opened the door,
there was the Host Club.
扉を開けると
そこは…ホスト部でした
"Starting Today, You are a Host!"
Those with the wherewithal
この私立桜蘭学院は
- first, in social standing,
and second, in money-
一に家柄　二にお金
spend their time here,
at the private Ouran Academy.
財あるものは暇を持つ
As such, Ouran Host Club
is where handsome boys
かくして桜蘭ホスト部とは
暇を持て余す美少年たちが
with too much time on their hands
entertain and charm girls,
同じく暇な女生徒たちを持て成し　潤わす
who also have too much
time on their hands.
It is the school's own personal,
elegant playground for the super-rich.
スーパー金持ち学校独自の 華麗なる遊戯なのである
ホ…ホ…ホスト部？
H-Host Club?
Oh, it's a boy.
なんだ　男か
Hikaru and Kaoru, this visitor
is in the same class as you, right?
光と馨はこのお客様と同じクラスだろ
Yes, he is, but he isn't very sociable,
so we don't know him too well.
そうだけど
この人付き合い悪いから　よく知らない
It's impolite to say it like that.
そんな言い方は失礼だぞ
Welcome to Ouran Host Club,
Honor Student.
桜蘭ホスト部へようこそ
特待生さん
What? Then, this exceptionally rare
何？！
では世にも稀な特待生の藤岡ハルヒとは君のことか
honor student we've heard about,
Fujioka Haruhi, is you?
How do you know my name?
なんで名前…
It's just that our school tradition makes
it difficult for commoners to get in.
どうもうちの校風は庶民には敷居が高すぎるらしくてね
"Commoner"
I've been told that unless you
possess a rather audacious nerve,
よほど図太い神経の持ち主でなきゃ
"Audacious" "Commoner"
you cannot become an honor student here.
特待生にはなれないだろうと言わていたんだ
Why... thank you...
そりゃどうも
Yes! He's saying that you
are a hero, Fujioka- kun!
そう　いわば君は勇者だ　藤岡君
Even though you might
be at the head of the class,
例え学年首席であろうと
you are still the poorest person
in the whole school.
君は学校一の貧乏人
Maybe you lowly people
are looked down upon.
下賤の民と蔑まれるかもしれない
No, I wouldn't necessarily go that far.
いや　別にそこまで言われる筋合いは…
いいじゃないか 貧乏万歳だ
It doesn't matter, does it?
Long live the poor!
Welcome to our world of beauty, poor man!
麗しの世界にようこそ 大貧民よ
Excuse me.
失礼します
Hey! Haru-chan! Haru-chan!
Haru-chan, you're a hero? Amazing!
ねぇ　ハルちゃん　ハルちゃん
ハルちゃんは勇者なの すごいなぁ
I'm not a hero, I'm just an honor student.
勇者じゃなくて特待生…
って　誰がハルちゃんだ？！
And who are you calling "Haru-chan"?
Still, to think that such a fabled,
erudite student would be gay...
しかし　噂のガリ勉君が男色家だったとは
へぇ？男色？
Gay?
What is your preference?
どんなのがお好みかな
The wild type?
ワイルド系？
The boy Lolita type?
ロリショタ系？
小悪魔系？
The little devil type?
The cool type?
クール系？
I-it's not like that!
ち…違います
I was just looking for a quiet place
where I could study.
自分はただ静かに勉強できる所を探して…
Or maybe...
それとも
...you'd like to try me? How about it?
この俺にしてみる　いっちゃう
The Renaissance vase that was
to be featured in the school auction!
校内オークションの目玉予定だったルネの花瓶が…
Now you've done it.
困ったねぇ
We were going to start the bidding
at 8 million yen for that!
これ八百万円から吹っ掛けようと思ってたんだよね
8 million yen!?
八百万円？！　って　何千円だっけ
How many thousand yen is that?
How many thousands are in 8 million?
八百万って何千円　えっと
Um, can I pay you back?
あの　弁償…
Could you even?
できんの 指定の制服も買えない人が
You can't even afford
the designated uniform.
What is that grubby outfit, anyway?
大体なんなんの そのダサイ格好
What will it be, Tamaki?
どうする　環
Have you ever heard this
saying, Fujioka- kun?
こういう諺をご存知かな　藤岡君
"When in Rome, do as the Romans do!"
郷に入っては　郷に従え
If you have no money,
then pay with your body.
金がなければ体で払え
"Sudden change in attitude"
今日から君はホスト部の犬だ
Starting today, you are
the Host Club's dog!
"Dog"
"Host Club Dog"
This is too much, Mom.
あんまりです　お母さん
I've been captured by a ridiculous bunch
who call themselves a ''Host Club.''
自分はホスト部とかいうわけの分からん連中に
捕まってしまいました
Poke, poke.
"The Host Club is now open for business"
Tamaki- kun, what's your favorite music?
楽は？
That one tune, that reminds me of you,
もちろん君との思い出のあの曲さ
of course.
I baked you a cake today.
Would you have some for me?
今日はケーキを焼いてきたの　食べてくれる？
"High School 2nd Year,
Tamaki Suou (Host Club King)"
If you will feed it to me.
君が食べさせてくれるなら
Oh, Tamaki- kun!
ヤダ　環君ったら
Tamaki-sama, I heard...
環さま　聞きましてよ
You're keeping an
unpedigreed little kitten?
血統書のない子猫を育ててらっしゃるんですって
I wouldn't say a kitten, more like...
子猫というよりは…
Oh, speak of the devil.
おっ　噂をすれば…
Thanks for shopping for us, little piglet.
子豚ちゃん　買出しご苦労
Did you get everything bought all right?
ちゃんと買えたかにゃ
"High School 1st Year,
Haruhi Fujioka (Host Club Dog)"
ぶ…豚…
P-pig?
So, what's this, then?
で　これは何かな
Just what it looks like, it's coffee.
見ての通り　コーヒーですが
I've never seen this name brand.
見たことないメーカーだなぁ
Is this the kind that's already ground?
すでに碾いてあるやつか
No, it's instant.
じゃなくて　インスタントです
Instant?
インスタント？
Oh, commoners' coffee, where you only
have to add hot water, right?
お湯を注ぐだけでできるという　あの庶民コーヒーか
Ooh, I've heard of this.
まっ　それが噂の…
So it's true about poor people
not having any free time,
貧乏な方は暇がないので
豆も碾けないというのは本当でしたのね
so they can't even grind
their own beans, huh?
Commoners have their wisdom.
庶民の知恵だな
It says that 100g costs 300 yen.
百グラム三百円だって
That's an incredible price drop.
凄まじい価格破壊だね
I'll go buy something else.
買い直してきます
Excuse me for not getting expensive beans.
すいませんね　高い豆じゃなくて
No, wait!
いや　待って
I'll drink this.
俺は飲む
飲んで見せるぞ
I'll drink this, all right!
All right, Haruhi,
よし　ハルヒ　こっちに来て庶民コーヒーを淹れてみよう
come over here and make
this commoners' coffee.
Damn these rich people...
くそ　金持ちどもめ
Oh, Tamaki-sama,
you carry the joke too far.
環さまったら　お戯れが過ぎますわね
There's no way that
such a lowly person's drink
下賎な者の買うしコーヒーがお口に合うはずありませんのに
will be to your taste.
Huh?
Forgive me.
ごめんなさい　独り言よ
I was talking to myself.
ハルヒ
Haruhi!
Okay, okay...
"Demonstration of commoners' coffee,
by a commoner"
There you go.
どうぞ
Let the tasting begin.
お試しあれ
I'm a little scared to drink this.
飲むのはちょっと怖いかも
If I drink this,
my father will yell at me.
こんなの口にしたらお父様に叱られちゃう
What if you drank it from my mouth?
口移しならどうかな
I-I'd drink it.
の…飲みます
Good grief...
そんで　こいつったら　怖い夢見たって飛び起きてさあ
So then, he had this terrible dream,
and when he bolted up from it...
Hikaru! Not that story!
光…その話は…
You're awful, telling that story
in front of others.
ひどいよ　みんなの前でそんな話…
馨
Kaoru...
"High School 1st Years,
Hikaru & Kaoru Hitachiin"
I'm sorry, Kaoru.
ごめんよ　馨
You were just so cute when it happened,
I couldn't help myself.
あの時のお前が可愛かったから つい…
Hikaru...
光
"The"very close"Hitachiin twins."
Waah! What beautiful brotherly love!
麗しき兄弟愛よ
Why are they crying for joy?
I don't understand at all.
なぜ泣いて喜ぶ　さっぱり分からん
ごめん　遅れた
I'm sorry, I'm late.
ハニー君　モリ君
Honey- kun! Mori- kun!
We've been waiting
this whole time for you!
もう　ずっと待ってたのよ
I'm sorry.
ごめん
"High School 3rd-Year,
Takashi Morinozuka ('Mori' for short)"
崇の掛け持ち剣道部終わるの待ってたら つい寝ちゃって
I was waiting for Takashi
to get out of his swordsmanship club,
but I drifted off to sleep.
"High School 3rd-Year,
Mitsukuni Haninozuka ('Honey' for short)"
And I still seem to be sleepy.
なんだか　まだ眠い
可愛いぃぃぃ
How cute!
Is that boy really a 3rd-Year?
本当に三年生なのかな　あの人
Honey-senpai is a prodigy,
despite his appearance.
ハニー先輩はああ見えて秀才でいらっしゃる
And Mori-senpai's draw
is his silent disposition.
そしてモリ先輩は　寡黙さが売りなんだ
Haru-chan!
ハルちゃん
Haru-chan, want to have some cake with me?
ハルちゃんも一緒にケーキ食べる？
No, I don't really like sweets...
いえ　甘いものはちょっと…
Well, I'll let you borrow
my bunny, Usa-chan!
じゃ　僕のウサちゃん貸してあげる
No, I'm not up for Usa-chan, either.
いや　ウサちゃんもちょっと…
僕のウサちゃん　嫌い？
You don't like my Usa-chan?
I-it is cute, huh?
か…可愛いですね
Take good care of it, okay?
大事にしてねぇ
Our club's policy is to utilize
everyone's individual characteristics,
うちの部は各自の特性を活かし
お客様のニーズに応えるのが方針でね
to respond to the needs of our guests.
By the way, around here,
Tamaki is number-one, the king.
ちなみに　環がうちのナンバーワン　キングだ
His request rate is 70 percent.
指名率七割だよ
What is the world coming to?
世も末ですね
"High School 2nd-Year,
Kyoya Otori (Vice-president)"
By the way, with your 8 million yen debt,
ところで　借金八百万円の君は
you are this club's dog
until you graduate-
とりあえず卒業するまではこの部の犬…
oh, pardon me, errand boy.
失礼　雑用係りだ
You're free to run away,
逃げるのは自由だが
but my family employs an able,
private police force of roughly 100.
我が家には有能なプライベートポリスが
ざっと百人ほど揃っていてね
Do you have a passport?
君　パスポート持ってる？
"Meaning, 'you won't be able
to stay in Japan'."
Yeah, be sure to work hard,
そうよ　しっかり働いてね　ダサ岡君
"Dasa-oka"- kun.
[Dasa-uncool, lame, unfashionable]
やめてください
Please don't do that.
You're not going to get any girls,
as disheveled as you look.
そんなダサダサじゃ  女の子にもてないぞ
I'm not interested in getting
any in the first place.
基本的にそういうの興味ないんです
What are you talking about?
This is important.
何を言う　大切なことだぞ
Becoming a fine man,
and pleasing the ladies, is everything.
いい男は女を喜ばせることがすべてだ
It doesn't matter either way, does it?
どうでもよくないですか
Men, women, appearances, and such?
男とか女とか外見とか
What's important as a person
is what's on the inside, right?
人間　大切なのは中身でしょう
I can't understand why
this kind of club even exists.
なんでこんな部があるのかもさっぱりだ
It's such a cruel thing, isn't it?
残酷なものだよね
Once in a while,
神は時として器も中身も完璧な人間を作り出してしまう
God creates the perfect person,
both inside and out.
Huh?
I understand how you must feel,
wanting to console yourself like that.
君がそうして自分を慰めたい気持ちは分かるさ
Otherwise, you couldn't go on living, huh?
そうしなきゃ　生きていけないのね
だがよく考えてみたまえ
But think hard about it.
Why do they put museum pieces in museums?
美術館に美術品があるのはなんのためだ
Yes, it is the duty of those
who were born beautiful
そう　美しいものを見せびらかすのは
- What was it that you call...
- to show off beautiful things.
美しく生まれたものの義務だ
何って言うんだっけ　ああいう人のこと
...people like this again?
- Which is the reason why
I started this club,
そんなわけで俺は　美に飢えてる人々のために
- for the sake of those
who are starved for beauty,
- Let's see...
- for the sake of those
who are starved for beauty,
この部を立ち上げ　日夜努力惜しまず　美を追求している
- Let's see...
- and work unsparingly, day and night,
in the pursuit of beauty.
- Hmm... what was it again?
- With your looks,
君の容貌では　不必要な技術だが
ええと　何だっけなぁ
- Hmm... what was it again?
- they may be needless skills,
- but as long as I have the opportunity,
せっかくだから
この俺の華麗な技の一部を教えてやろう
- Hmm... what was it again?
- I shall share a portion
of my magnificent expertise with you.
When placing your glass down, be sure
to extend your pinky finger first,
グラスを置く時は
必ず小指でワンクッションいれてから置くこと
as a cushion.
That makes it more difficult
to raise a clatter,
がしにくいし　置く位置も掴みやすい
- Hmm...
- and easier to clasp it
where you have set it.
- Hmm...
- It looks more refined
that way, doesn't it?
その方が品良く見えるだろう
面倒…じゃなくて　もっとこう　的確な言い方が…
など立てぬもの
- ''A pain in the neck''?
- Fine men do not make
any uncouth sounds.
グラス越しに映る自分も好き
- No, there's a more precise expression...
- I also like to look
at my reflection in the glass.
Also, the most important
thing to remember...
そして　ここ一番の時には
...is how effective
looking up at an angle is.
下からのアングラが効果的だ
Oh, I got it!
そっか
- Did I strike a chord?
- Obnoxious.
ドキっとしたかにゃ
ウザイ
Um... Tamaki-senpai?
あの　環先輩？
You're a hero, all right!
やっぱりお前勇者だな
He is a pain in the neck, though.
面倒な人だなぁ
I'm sorry. It really did strike
a small chord with me.
すみません　本当は少しドキッとしました
そうかそうか
I see, I see! Then allow me to share
yet another skill with you!
では更なる技も教えてやろう
He gets over things quickly.
立ち直り早っ
Sir...
殿…
Call me "King"!
キングと呼べ
You can teach the basics
of hosting as much as you want...
いくらホストの手解きしたって
...but in his case,
彼の場合
he hasn't even passed the first,
most basic visual test.
一番基本のビジュアル面をクリアしてないでしょう
Now, with someone of his type,
even if you take off his glasses,
まっ　この手のタイプは眼鏡を取っても
his eyes just look that much smaller...
さらに目が小さくなるくらいで…
Hey, now!
あっ　ちょっと…
I lost my contacts the day
of the school's opening ceremony.
入学式の日にコンタクトなくしちゃったんだから…
Hikaru! Kaoru!
光　馨
Yes, sir!
Kyoya, contact the hair designer!
鏡夜は　ヘアデザイナーに連絡
Mori-senpai, to the doctor,
to arrange for contact lenses!
モリ先輩は　コンタクトレンズの手配を　保健医の先生へ
Tama-chan, what about me?
タマちゃん　僕は？
Honey-senpai...
ハニー先輩は
Mm-hmm?
Please go have some cake.
ケーキ食べててください
You know what?
あのね　みんな忙しいんだって
Everyone else said they were too busy.
さあ　これに着替えるんだ
Here! Change into this!
What? What!
Don't ask any questions!
問答無用
No way!
いやだ 分かった　着替えるから　二人とも外出てて
All right, I'll change,
but you two have to get out!
Whoa-oa-oa-oa...
"Changing Room"
Um, Senpai?
あのう　先輩
Oh, are you done changing?
おっ　着替えられたかにゃ
I can really keep this uniform?
この制服　もらっていいんですか
なんて可愛いんだ　まるで女の子じゃないか
How adorable!
You almost look like a girl, don't you?
Haru-chan, how cute!
ハルちゃん　可愛い
"Complete uniform, 300,000 yen"
If that's how you really look...
そんな顔してんなら
...you should have said so sooner.
早く言ってよね
Might even be able to draw
some customers like that.
これなら客もつくんじゃないか
Yes! It's all just as I figured!
そうよ　すべて計算通り
"Bullcrap..."
The errand boy has graduated!
雑用係りは卒業
Starting today, you are an official
member of the Host Club!
今日から君はホスト部の正式部員だ
俺が一流のホストに育ててやる
I will train you to be
a first-rate host.
If you can get 100 customers
to request you,
もし百人の指名客を集められたら
we will forgive your 8 million yen debt.
借金の八百万はチャラにしてやろう
A host?
ホスト？！
"Haruhi is also now open for business"
Haruhi- kun...
ハルヒ君
Haruhi- kun, what hobbies do you have?
ハルヒ君のご趣味は何
Do you do anything special to your skin?
お肌の手入れは何か特別なことを？
It's terribly pretty.
すごくきれい
I-I can't do this...
だ…だめだ
I have no idea what I should be doing.
何をしたらいいのかさっぱりだ
Haruhi- kun, why did you join this club?
ハルヒ君はどうしてこの部に？
That's right,
そうだ　百人の指名客を集めたら
once I get 100 customers to request me,
they'll forgive my 8 million yen debt.
八百万の借金はチャラ
I have just the story.
これは　そういう話…
I see, your mother passed away
ten years ago, after being sick?
お母様は十年前にご病気で…
So, who does the domestic chores?
それじゃ　家事なんかは？
Oh, I do those by myself.
自分でやります
My mother was good at cooking,
母は料理の得意な人で
and she left me lots of recipes
when she was in the hospital.
入院中レシピをたくさん残してくれたんです
Learning each one of them is fun to do,
それをひとつずつ覚えるのは楽しいし
and on days when they turn out well,
my father is delighted, too.
うまくできた日は　父も喜んでくれて
そういう時間が自分はとても好きなんです
Those are the times that I really like.
Um...
あのう
Tomorrow, could we...
私たち明日も
...request you once again?
指名してよろしいかしら
Oh, I would appreciate that.
それは助かります
- He's popular, right from the start.
- A real natural.
のっけから受け取る
天然だな
No help needed.
テクいらず
Tamaki-sama...
環さま
ごめんよ　姫
Oh, I'm sorry, my princess.
I'm just a little concerned
about my boy.
ちょっとうちの子が気になってしまってねぇ
You seem to be keeping an eye
ずいぶんとあの子には目をかけていらっしゃるのね
on that one quite a bit.
That's because I'm raising him
like he was my own.
それはもう　我が子のように育ててます
Haruhi! Come here for a minute.
ハルヒ　ちょっとこちらへ
Yes?
Say hello. This is my regular guest,
ご挨拶しろ
俺のお得意さま　綾小路姫だ
Princess Ayanokoji.
Oh, that girl from earlier.
あっ　この間の…
どうぞ　よろしく
It's a pleasure to meet you.
"Just smile and continue"
か…可愛いぞ　ハルヒ
That was so cute, Haruhi!
That air of bashfulness was good,
good, very good!
そのはにかんだ感じがgood good very good
T-Tamaki-sama...
環さま
- M-Mori-senpai!
- I'm not letting you go!
モリ先輩　助けて
放さないよ　放さない　はなっ　はなさっ
Help!
Mori-senpai, you didn't
have to go that far.
モリ先輩　何もそこまでしなくても…
Come on, come back
next to Daddy's heart!
ほら　お父さんの胸に戻っておいで
I don't need two fathers.
二人も父は要りません
Huh? My bag is gone.
あれ　カバンがない
Aw, man...
あっちゃ
I didn't think there was any
bullying at this school,
この学園に苛めはないと思ってたけど
これはさすがに…
but sure enough...
Oh, it's you.
あら　あなた
How nice for you, to have
Tamaki-sama tidy you up.
環さまのおかげで小奇麗になれてよかったわねぇ
While you're at it,
ついでに育ちの悪さも直したらいかがかしら
why don't you correct
your poor upbringing?
Well, that was probably
the guilty party,
まぁ　犯人はあの人なんだろうけど
and whatever her reasons were,
理由はともかく
I have to find my wallet,
財布が見つからないと　今週の食費が…
or I won't have any money
for food this week.
ほら　庶民
Hey, commoner!
You've got some nerve,
skipping out on your club activities.
部活をサボるとはいい度胸だなぁ
Why is your bag all wet?
なんだ　カバン濡らして
I just dropped it.
ちょっと落としちゃって
I can't find my food money for this week.
今週の食費が見つからないんです
That's okay. You'll get yourself all wet.
いいですよ　濡れちゃうし
Getting wet isn't going
to do any harm, is it?
濡れるぐらいいいじゃないか
People always say that I'm dripping
with good looks, after all.
水も滴るいい男って言うだろうが
Oh, might this be...
探していたものは
...what you're looking for?
これかにゃ
What's the matter? You're off in space.
どうした　ぼうっとして
You haven't fallen for me, have you?
俺に惚れちゃったかにゃ
誰が
Who, me?
Still, how does something
like this happen?
しかし　どうしてこんなことに？
そのう…
Well...
I accidentally dropped it out the window.
うっかりして　窓から落としちゃったんですよ
I see. That must have been terrible, huh?
そう　それは大変だったわね
Having your bag fall
into the pond all on its own...
カバンが独りでに池に落ちるなんて
なぜこの人が自分に指名を…
Why would she request me?
Although, to make Tamaki-sama
go to all the trouble
でも　薄汚いカバンを拾うために
of picking up your grimy bag for you,
環さまの手を煩わせるとは
you really don't know
your own place, do you?
あまりの身の程知らずね
Tamaki-sama is only
paying you any attention
環さまがあなたを構うのは育ちが珍しいからよ
because your upbringing
was so unusual.
Don't go getting any ideas
as to why he's doting on you.
可愛がられてるなんて勘違いしないことね
So what you mean is...
それは　つまり…
...you're jealous?
ヤキモチ
ハルヒ君が…ハルヒ君が突然乱暴なことを…
Haruhi- kun...
Haruhi- kun suddenly attacked me!
誰か　早く　この庶民を…
Somebody, quick!
Deal with this commoner!
なっ　何をするの
What are you doing?
Tamaki-sama, Haruhi- kun assaulted me.
環さま　ハルヒ君が私に…
見苦しいな
How disgraceful.
You're the one who threw
Haruhi's bag in the pond, aren't you?
ハルヒのカバンを池に捨てたろ
How can you say that?
Do you have any proof?
そんな　なにか証拠でも？
You really are quite pretty,
君はなかなかきれいなんだけど
but you are not fit to be our guest.
うちの客には相応しくないね
I know this much-
俺には分かってる
Haruhi is not that kind of man.
ハルヒはそんな男じゃない
た…環さまの　バカ
T-Tamaki-sama, you idiot!
I'm going to decide your punishment
for causing this trouble.
お前には 揉め事を起こした罰を言い渡す
Your quota is increased to 1000 yen!
追加ノルマ　千人
1000 yen?
千…人…
Here.
I'm expecting much from you,
期待してるぞ
natural rookie.
天然ルーキー
This is the only spare uniform we have.
予備の制服はこれしかない
It's still better than that
wet one, though, right?
濡れたままよりはましだろう
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
"Changing Room"
Haruhi, here...
ハルヒ
ほぃ　タオルだ
Some towels.
Haruhi...
ハルヒ
Yes?
"Female"
You're a girl?
お前　女なのか
Biologically, yes.
"Student ID"
"Fujioka, Haruhi Male / Female"
"Ouran Academy High School President"
生物学上は　一応
Senpai, if you all think of me as a boy,
先輩たちが男と思っているなら
then that's okay with me, too.
別にそれでもいいかなぁっと
My feeling is...
どうも自分は男とか女の意識が人よりも低いらしくて
that any awareness
of being a boy or a girl
falls lower than that
of being a person.
"Knew it from the start"
かなり面白い展開だな
This is quite an interesting development.
"Figured it out along the way"
It sure is.
本当
Still, Senpai,
でも　先の先輩　ちょっと格好良かったですよ
you were kind of cool earlier.
Could this possibly
be the beginnings of love?
ひょっとしてこういうのもひとつの恋の始まりでは？
You know, being a host,
and getting fussed over by girls
だけど　ホストになって　女の子にちやほやされるのも
悪くないですね
might not be all that bad.
I know!
そうだ
From now on, I'll start using "ore."
今度から　「俺」って言おう
人気があるからっていい気になっちゃいかんぞ
Don't get too full of yourself,
just because you're popular.
ホストと言うものはだなぁ
- lf you're going to be a host...
- Oh, another customer has requested me.
またお客さんが指名してくれてる
Don't go taking my customers!
俺の客をとるな
Next time, "The Job of a High School Host"
Ouran High School Host Club
will be waiting for you, next week!
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ 来週も
お待ちしております